(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T14:04:43.764153",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Out Now!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous"
「Sincerely」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Sincerely"
Mini Album STAR A·R·T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR A·R·T" Release!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawaikute Gomen" Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Out Now!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous"
「Sincerely」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Sincerely"
Mini Album STAR A·R·T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR A·R·T" Release!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawaikute Gomen" Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Out Now!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous"
「Sincerely」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Sincerely"
Mini Album STAR A·R·T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR A·R·T" Release!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawaikute Gomen" Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Out Now!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous"
「Sincerely」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Sincerely"
Mini Album STAR A·R·T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR A·R·T" Release!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawaikute Gomen" Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Out Now!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous"
「Sincerely」(Cover)
AZKi Cover: "Sincerely"
Mini Album STAR A·R·T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR A·R·T" Release!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawaikute Gomen" Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
ELTAMA Bento Project Participant List & Thanks
本日は、ソラアズ メジャーデビューライブ ファースト グラビティ @クラブチッタにご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending the SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" at CLUB CITTA' today.
開演に先立ちまして、ソラマメの皆様にお願いしたいことをお伝えします。
Before the show starts, we would like to ask a few things of all Soramame.
客席内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為は禁止となります。
Mosh pits, diving, jumping, and other dangerous activities in the seating area are prohibited.
以上のことが守られない場合は、公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただく可能性がございます。
If these rules are not followed, there is a possibility that the performance may be temporarily suspended or canceled.
ペンライトは周りのお客さまのご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮お願いします。
Please be considerate with penlights so as not to disturb surrounding guests.
頭の上に出したり、大きく左右に振りますと、後ろのお客さまや周りのお客さまのご迷惑となる場合がございます。
Holding penlights above your head or swinging them widely left and right may cause inconvenience to guests behind or around you.
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご容赦ください。
Staff may give you instructions, so please understand.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、お客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for video streaming and photography will enter the venue during this performance, and your appearance may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These videos and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes, so please understand in advance.
客席内での携帯電話は、スマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones in the seating area is prohibited.
携帯電話や音の鳴る機械の電源はあらかじめお切り下さいますようお願い申し上げます。
Please make sure to turn off mobile phones and noise-making devices in advance.
また携帯、え、携帯電話、スマートフォン等による撮影、録音、録画は固くお断りいたします。
Also, filming, recording, or taking pictures with mobile phones or smartphones is strictly prohibited.
万が一発見した場合はデータ削除の上、ご退場していただく場合がございます。
In the unlikely event that this is discovered, you may be asked to delete the data and leave the venue.
最後にライブの途中で具合が悪くなったりしたらお近くのスタッフにお声がけください。
Lastly, if you feel unwell during the live performance, please speak to nearby staff.
また地震、火災などの非常時は慌てずスタッフの誘導に従って避難していただきますようお願いいたします。
Also, in emergencies such as earthquakes or fires, please evacuate calmly following staff guidance.
配信でご視聴のお客さまへ、本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
To viewers watching the stream, recording, screen-mirroring, or illegal uploading of this live performance is strictly prohibited.
その代わりスクリーンショットを撮影して映像とともにSNSに投稿していただくは大歓迎です。
Instead, taking screenshots and posting them on SNS along with video is warmly welcomed.
本公演のハッシュタグはソラアズグラビティとなります。
The hashtag for this performance is #SoraAzuGravity.
思い出でしょ？
That's a memory, right?
もしかして
Could it be...
ねえ、みんな聞こえてますかーー？
Hey, can everyone hear meーー?
聞こえてるー？
Can you hear me?
聞こえてる！
I can hear you!
マイクテスト！マイクテストだよー！
Mic test! It's a mic test!
マイクテスト！みんな聞こえてますかー！
Mic test! Can everyone hear me?!
ねえー、聞こえて……は、ないともー！
Hey, can you... no, you can't, right?!
空、空から……みんなを見守ってるよー！
From the sky... I'm watching over everyone!
見えてますか？
Can you see me?
多分これからは見えます。時の空で！あずきでーす！
You'll probably see me now. With Tokino Sora! I'm AZKi!
ゲリラだよ、ゲリラ！
It's a guerrilla stream!
みんな今どんな気持ち？そんな言い方は……いいのかな？
How is everyone feeling? Is that... a good way to put it?
そんな気持ちを……ソラズグラビティでポストしてください！
Please post your feelings with #SorazGravity!
ポストしてくれる人……？あー！やったー！
Anyone going to post...? Ah! Yay!
ありがとう！トレンド入り目指していこう！イエーイ！
Thank you! Let's aim for the trending list! Yay!
すごい、みんな、みんな愛してくれてるー！
Wow, everyone, everyone loves me so much!
タオルステは……あ、タオルしてくれてる！タオル！
Towel ste... Oh, you're using towels! Towels!
熱いの？熱い！これからもっと熱くなりますから。
Is it hot? Hot! It's going to get even hotter from here.
みんな気をつけて。あ、じゃあ、みんな仲良くぬんぬんしながらライブ見、ね、ライブ楽しんでこね。
Everyone take care. Get along and nun-nun while enjoying the live!
なんあす、なんあす、なんあす！
Nan-Az, Nan-Az, Nan-Az!
え？じゃあみんなもう少し持っててください。
Eh? Well then, everyone hold on to it a little longer.
ぬんがざーい！
Nungazai!
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' January 27 CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Bento Catering Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'San Maime no Chizu' Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
'Sincerely' (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR A*T
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR A*T' Releases March 6, 2024
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: 'Kawaikute Gomen'
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' January 27 CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Bento Catering Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'San Maime no Chizu' Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
'Sincerely' (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR A*T
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR A*T' Releases March 6, 2024
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: 'Kawaikute Gomen'
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' January 27 CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Bento Catering Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'San Maime no Chizu' Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
'Sincerely' (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR A*T
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR A*T' Releases March 6, 2024
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: 'Kawaikute Gomen'
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' January 27 CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Bento Catering Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'San Maime no Chizu' Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
'Sincerely' (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR A*T
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR A*T' Releases March 6, 2024
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: 'Kawaikute Gomen'
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' January 27 CD Purchase Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Bento Catering Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'San Maime no Chizu' Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
'Sincerely' (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR A*T
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR A*T' Releases March 6, 2024
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: 'Kawaikute Gomen'
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Released December 20, 2023
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Tokino Sora Cover: "So Cute I'm Sorry"
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Goods Purchase Bonus
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Tokino Sora Cover: "So Cute I'm Sorry"
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Goods Purchase Bonus
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Tokino Sora Cover: "So Cute I'm Sorry"
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Goods Purchase Bonus
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Tokino Sora Cover: "So Cute I'm Sorry"
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Goods Purchase Bonus
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Tokino Sora Cover: "So Cute I'm Sorry"
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Goods Purchase Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」 (Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
Mini Album STAR*T リリース決定！
Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」 (Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
Mini Album STAR*T リリース決定！
Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」 (Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
Mini Album STAR*T リリース決定！
Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」 (Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
Mini Album STAR*T リリース決定！
Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」 (Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
Mini Album STAR*T リリース決定！
Mini Album "STAR*T" Release Confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Bonus
メジャーデビューEP 3枚目の地図 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
ときのそら ミニアルバム「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Releasing!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawakute Gomen" Out Now!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Out Now!
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "San Maime no Chizu" Out Now!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Out Now!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
ときのそら ミニアルバム「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Releasing!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawakute Gomen" Out Now!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Out Now!
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 1)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 2)
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 3)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 4)
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "San Maime no Chizu" Out Now!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Out Now!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
ときのそら ミニアルバム「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Releasing!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawakute Gomen" Out Now!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Out Now!
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 1)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 2)
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 3)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 4)
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "San Maime no Chizu" Out Now!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Out Now!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
ときのそら ミニアルバム「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Releasing!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawakute Gomen" Out Now!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Out Now!
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 1)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 2)
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 3)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 4)
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "San Maime no Chizu" Out Now!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Out Now!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
ときのそら ミニアルバム「STAR*T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR*T" Releasing!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Cover "Kawakute Gomen" Out Now!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Out Now!
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Bonus
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 1)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 2)
エルタマ お弁当 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 3)
Bento & Gift Sponsorship Participant Credits (Page 4)
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "San Maime no Chizu" Out Now!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Out Now!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Out Now!
せーのっ！せーのっ！
Ready, set! Ready, set!
深呼吸 始まってく ここから
Take a deep breath, starting right from here,
レディゴー！！
ready go!!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming!
最高だよ！
You're the best!
大危険 突き抜けて
Breaking through extreme danger,
イメージも 歌声も
both my image and my singing voice
意識を 飛び越えて 響く
surpass consciousness and echo out.
キラキラ キラキラ
Sparkling, sparkling,
照らすの 小宇宙
illuminating the microcosm.
ただ 良い巡り合い
Just a wonderful encounter,
瞬時 同期する 奇跡って
what a miraculous instant synchronization.
ビリビリ 高まって
Tingling and intensifying,
くるくる回る みんな
everyone spinning around
ミラーボール
like a mirror ball.
私たちが夢のファーストブレス 思い切り遊ぼう
This is our dream first breath, let's play to our heart's content!
AZとZ 空をかけて 振り切っちゃってこう
AZ and Z, soaring across the sky, let's break all limits!
科学反応を生み出す光 今ここで繋がった
The light born from chemical reactions is connected right here now.
照らして 照らし合って せーのっ
Illuminating, lighting each other up, ready, set—
頷いて 始まってく
Nodding, it's starting,
ワンダー レディゴー
wonder ready go!
トキメキ タップして
Tap into the excitement,
ひらくわ 新時代
and open up a new era.
可能性 蘇生は なんて
Possibility resurrection is... how should I put it?
アメージングだね
It's amazing, isn't it?
ふたりの エーテルに 時々 伝播する
The ether between us occasionally propagating,
嗜好色 一緒でしょ 生きるって
our favorite colors are the same, that's what living is.
運命の シンコペーション
Fate's syncopation,
星屑のナウェイから 投げる
throwing from the Stardust runway.
虹の彼方 光るフューチャーサイン
Beyond the rainbow, a glowing future sign,
キャッチして グロリアス
catch it, glorious!
愛という 奏でるのは ミラクルでいい
What we play called love, a miracle is fine.
維新伝心で バレるテレパス
Heart-to-heart telepathy exposed.
今という 瞬間を 感じて 感じ合って
Feeling this very moment, feeling it together,
せーのっ！ 深呼吸 見たことないワンダー
ready, set! Take a deep breath, an unseen wonder,
君と 心躍らせよう
let's make our hearts dance with you!
思いと 思いが 作る世界
A world created by feelings and thoughts,
ここにある ここにいるよ 歌を 歌えば
it's right here, I'm right here, if we sing a song,
ひとつになれる もっと なれるよ
we can become one, even more so!
自由に ようこそ ここはバイアスーム
Welcome to freedom, here is the bias-free room.
ふたりの エキスト ガラパゴススペース
The two of us in an extra Galapagos space.
私たちが夢のファーストブレス 思い切り遊ぼう
This is our dream first breath, let's play to our heart's content!
AZとZ 空をかけて 振り切っちゃってこう
AZ and Z, soaring across the sky, let's break all limits!
科学反応を生み出す光 今ここで繋がった
The light born from chemical reactions is connected right here now.
照らして 照らし合って せーのっ
Illuminating, lighting each other up, ready, set—
深呼吸 どこまでも行こうよ
taking a deep breath, let's go anywhere!
頷いて 始まってく ワンダー
Nodding, it starts, wonder.
レディゴー！ もっと遠くまで行こうよ
Ready go! Let's go even further!
頷いて 始まってく ワンダー
Nodding, it starts, wonder.
レディゴー！ 二人でも行くよ
Ready go! We'll go together too!
まだまだひるまずに 盛り上がって 次の曲も聞いちゃおう
Still not hesitating, let's get hyped and listen to the next song too!
さっき向こう側の気配 きっと目に映そう
That presence on the other side, surely reflected in our eyes.
誤魔化さず言って 言葉積み重ねよう
Say it without hiding, let's stack our words together.
高すぎる 壁さえも 飛んでしまうかな
Will we even be able to fly over walls that are too high?
通り抜けたって 何も楽しくないって
Passing right through isn't fun at all,
笑う君が教えてくれていたんだ
you laughed and taught me that.
夢を散々 かけ合わせ 時にはそう間違って
Multiplying dreams all over, sometimes making mistakes.
果てしない道のほうが
Taking the endless road...
冒険の旅をキミと 長く味わえるでしょ
makes our adventurous journey with you last longer, right?
からかわないで顔上げて
Lift your head up, don't tease me,
山あり谷ありの日々さ
days with ups and downs
ジェットコースターみたいじゃん
are just like a roller coaster!
小さなアイデアひとつで
With just one little idea,
世界は楽しく変わる
the world changes in a fun way.
すべてが僕らの遊び場 どこまで行こう?
All of it is our playground, how far shall we go?
夢がひとつあればいい カバンに詰め込んで
It's fine to have just one dream, packed in my bag,
胸の奥のドキドキ 止まらない未来へ
heading toward an unstoppable future with a pounding heart!
涙いくつこぼれても 仲間が集まれば
No matter how many tears fall, if friends gather around,
同じ数の笑顔 きっと見つけられるはずさ
we're sure to find the exact same number of smiles!
ケンカを我慢するより
Rather than holding back in a fight,
ケンカの後に必ず仲直りをしようよ
let's always make up right after!
小さなアイデアひとつで 世界は仲良くなれる
With just one little idea, the world can become friends.
まだ見ぬ僕らのトモダチ 探しに行こう!
Let's go look for our yet-unseen friends!
夢がひとつある限り 終わらない戦い
As long as we have one dream, the battle never ends,
勝ち負けよりトキメキ 忘れない心で
with a heart that never forgets the thrill over winning or losing!
キミがひとりいるだけで 勇気が溢れるよ
Just having you here makes courage overflow,
大きすぎる夢でも きっとかなえられるはずさ
surely even the grandest dream can come true!
小さなアイデアひとつで
With just one little idea,
世界は楽しく変わる
the world changes in a fun way.
すべてが僕らの遊び場 どこまで行こう?
All of it is our playground, how far shall we go?
夢がひとつあればいい カバンに詰め込んで
It's fine to have one dream, packed inside my bag,
胸の奥のドキドキ 止まらない未来へ
heading toward an unstoppable future with a pounding heart!
涙いくつこぼれても 仲間が集まれば
No matter how many tears fall, if friends gather around,
同じ数の笑顔 きっと見つけられるはずさ
we're sure to find the exact same number of smiles!
夢がひとつある限り 終わらない戦い
As long as we have one dream, the battle never ends,
勝ち負けよりトキメキ 忘れない心で
with a heart that never forgets the thrill over winning or losing!
キミがひとりいるだけで 勇気が溢れるよ
Just having you here makes courage overflow,
大きすぎる夢でも きっとかなえられるはずさ
surely even the grandest dream can come true!
小さなアイデアひとつで 世界は楽しく変わる
With just one little idea, the world changes in a fun way,
すべてが僕らの遊び場 どこまで行こう?
all of it is our playground, how far shall we go?
夢がひとつあればいい カバンに詰め込んで
It's fine to have one dream, packed inside my bag,
胸の奥のドキドキ 止まらない未来へ
heading toward an unstoppable future with a pounding heart!
涙いくつこぼれても 仲間が集まれば
No matter how many tears fall, if friends gather around,
同じ数の笑顔 きっと見つけられるはずさ
we're sure to find the exact same number of smiles!
夢がひとつある限り 終わらない戦い
As long as we have one dream, the battle never ends,
勝ち負けよりトキメキ 忘れない心で
with a heart that never forgets the thrill over winning or losing!
キミがひとりいるだけで 勇気が溢れるよ
Just having you here makes courage overflow,
大きすぎる夢でも きっとかなえられるはずさ
surely even the grandest dream can come true!
小さなアイデアひとつで 世界は楽しく変わる
With just one little idea, the world changes in a fun way,
すべてが僕らの遊び場 どこまで行こう?
all of it is our playground, how far shall we go?
夢がひとつあればいい カバンに詰め込んで
It's fine to have one dream, packed inside my bag,
胸の奥のドキドキ 止まらない未来へ
heading toward an unstoppable future with a pounding heart!
涙いくつこぼれても 仲間が集まれば
No matter how many tears fall, if friends gather around,
同じ数の笑顔 きっと見つけられるはずさ
we're sure to find the exact same number of smiles!
夢がひとつある限り 終わらない戦い
As long as we have one dream, the battle never ends,
勝ち負けよりトキメキ 忘れない心で
with a heart that never forgets the thrill over winning or losing!
キミがひとりいるだけで 勇気が溢れるよ
Just having you here makes courage overflow,
大きすぎる夢でも きっとかなえられるはずさ
surely even the grandest dream can come true!
教室から見上げた空
The sky I looked up at from the classroom,
四角い窓枠の向こう
beyond the square window frame...
太陽に負けない ヒカリ探そうよ
let's search for a light that won't lose to the sun!
○や×じゃ測れないさ
You can't measure it with circles and crosses,
答え合わせはいらない
we don't need to check answers.
正解のない日々さ ただ楽しもうよ
In these days without correct answers, let's just enjoy ourselves!
ノートの片隅 描かれた落書き
Scribbles drawn in the corner of the notebook,
現実に戻る瞬間を まあ、待ってる
waiting, well, for the moment we return to reality.
はみ出すよ 小さな自分を
Break out of your small self,
響かした声で仲間を引き寄せて
draw friends close with a resounding voice!
今 飛ぶよ 遥か彼方へ
Now, let's fly far away into the distance,
届きそうな勇気 かき集め抱きしめて
gathering up courage close enough to reach, and holding it tight!
チャイムに区切らせるな
Don't let the chime divide us,
僕らの信じる夢は…無限だから
because the dream we believe in is... infinite!
くよくよ失敗 はらはら心配よりか期待に期待に
Rather than dwelling on failures and nervously worrying, let's turn expectations into hopes,
ネガティブな感情 消しゴムで消そうよ
let's erase negative emotions with an eraser!
クラス分けじゃ離れないさ 同じハートのヤツとは
We won't be separated by class divisions, connected with those of the same heart,
つながっている めいっぱい頑張り合おうよ
let's do our absolute best together!
グラウンドの白線 踏み越えるみたいに
Like stepping over the white line of the ground,
流した涙も 乗り越えてみせたいんだ
we want to overcome even the tears we've shed!
はみ出すよ 今日の自分を
Break out of today's self,
革命は誰もルーティン壊し起こした
revolution is what anyone creates by breaking routine!
今 飛ぶよ 輝く未来
Now, let's fly into a shining future,
追い越せそうな元気バラまき 笑い合って
scattering energy that can overtake anything and smiling together!
遅刻はしない、約束
I promise I won't be late,
僕らの追う夢は…永遠だけど
though the dream we're chasing is... eternal!
はみ出すよ 小さな自分を
Break out of your small self,
響かした声で仲間を引き寄せて
draw friends close with a resounding voice!
今 飛ぶよ 遥か彼方へ
Now, let's fly far away into the distance,
届きそうな勇気 かき集め抱きしめて
gathering up courage close enough to reach, and holding it tight!
チャイムに区切らせるな
Don't let the chime divide us,
僕らの信じる夢は…無限だから
because the dream we believe in is... infinite!
いつか重力の鎖を断ち切り
Someday I'll break the chains of gravity
君を連れてサテライト
and take you with me to the satellite,
君を探してあの街へ
Searching for you to that town,
さ迷い歩いた夜の道
I wandered the night roads.
受話器越しに聞こえた声が
The voice I heard through the receiver
なぜかとても気になったの
why did it bother me so much?
見つけた君は赤い瞳
I found you with red eyes.
何もないふりはナシにして
Don't act like nothing's happening,
黒い沼に沈む君を
sinking in the black swamp—
放っておくわけにはいかない
I can't leave you behind.
いつか重力の鎖を解き放し
Someday releasing the chains of gravity,
宇宙へ飛ぶサテライト
flying into space to the satellite.
そこに行ければ体の重さも
Once you get there, your body weight
1/6
becomes one-sixth.
君が抱えている悲しみが
The sorrow you're holding—
少しでも軽くなればそれでいい
if it gets even a little lighter, that's fine.
いつかそこに君を連れていこう
Someday I'll take you there,
重力の外へ
beyond gravity.
宇宙旅行は無理ですが 物理的に高い所へ
Space travel is impossible, but physically to a high place,
色々考えてみた結果 目指すは港の赤い塔
after thinking about things, aiming for the red tower at the port.
走ってきたふりをして 胸の鼓動の速さを隠してみたの
Pretending to have run here, I tried to hide my racing heartbeat.
今日は君の手を救い上げる 権利をもらうよ
Today I get the right to lift your hand.
軌道エレベーターのように 雲を抜け昇るよサテライト
Like a space elevator, ascending through the clouds, the satellite.
300メートル昇れば 少しは軽くなるかもね
If you climb 300 meters, it might get a little lighter.
つまり子ドマシだけれど 意味が少しでも伝わればいい
In other words, a child's trick, but I hope the meaning gets across.
地上よりも上に連れていきたいの 重力の外へ
I want to take you higher than the ground, beyond gravity.
First Gravity
二人合わせて せーの
Together, ready, set—
ファーストグラビティ
First Gravity!
お待たせしました めっちゃ息切れてる
Sorry to keep you waiting! I'm completely out of breath.
お待たせしました皆さん！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
え、本日はソラアズメジャーデビューライブ「First Gravity」@クラブチッタ川崎公演にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to the SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" at CLUB CITTA' Kawasaki today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんなかなり待たせちゃったね、待っててくれてた？
You guys had to wait quite a while, huh? Were you waiting for us?
待っててくれたー
We were waiting!
いや今日はね、満員ということでみんなね体調には気をつけてぜひ最後まで楽しんでいってくださいね！
Today is a full house, so please take care of your health and enjoy yourselves all the way to the end!
みんなありがとう来てくれて！
Thank you everyone for coming!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
すごい、ありがとありがと
Amazing, thank you so much.
ということで、ん？
And so... huh?
えっと、最初にお知らせしておきましょうか。
Um, let's make an announcement first, shall we?
え、ここでYouTubeの無料配信は終わりになります。
The free YouTube broadcast ends here.
もっと見たいばっかり
"We want to see more!"
もっと見たいなと思ってくれたそこのおあなた！
You right there who thought you wanted to see more—
はい、どうぞありがとうありがとうありがとう！ありがとうありがとう！
Yes, please! Thank you, thank you, thank you! Thank you so much!
はい、ぜひですね、えっとね、概要欄かな？あとコメント欄にもあるかな？ここ、はい、ぜひチケット、え、配信チケットをご購入いただいて続きもぜひ見てください！
Please check the description box or comment section, purchase a streaming ticket, and make sure to watch the rest!
見てねー！すー！すー！
Watch it! Su! Su!
どうなったんだろ
I wonder how it turned out...
SorAZ Major Debut Live “First Gravity”
[SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity"]
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
This concludes the free preview.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
To watch the rest of the show, please purchase tickets via Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
The free preview ends here.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
To watch the rest of the main show, please purchase tickets on Ticket PIA.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
This concludes the free preview. To watch the rest, please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
The free preview ends here.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、
If you wish to watch the rest of the main feature,
チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
please purchase tickets on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
This concludes the free preview.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
To watch the rest, please purchase a ticket on Ticket PIA.